All right! Akimoto Hanaoka is going to make you fall in love with her!
I'll do my best!
This is the first time I've put one of these on.
I'll do my best.
Excuse me, Mr. Yoru.
I'll take three.
That's important.
I'm so embarrassed.
I'm embarrassed... and I'm laughing.
Isn't it awkward?
It's just a little too much tsundere for me.
Momotaro.
It's a challenge, isn't it?
I'll try my best to switch between the two for about 20 seconds.
I'll try my best.
This is a reading of Momotaro by Honoka Akimoto.
Once upon a time, there lived an old man and an old woman.
Ah...
Grandpa went to the mountains to mow the lawn
Grandma went to the river to wash clothes
While Grandma was washing her clothes in the river
A big peach came down the river
Next
Granny was washing her clothes in the river
What a big peach!
Granny carried it on her back and went home
And when she was about to cut the peach
And out of the peach came a big baby!
Oh, here comes the baby!
Wait, wait, wait!
They were so happy that they named him Momotaro.
They named him Momotaro.
Hmm?
Momotaro grew up quickly.
And became a fine, gentle boy.
A fine, gentle boy.
Wait! Wait!
Wait, wait, wait, it's hard!
So you've finished all three puzzles!
I've only gotten as far as naming him Momotaro.
What should I do?
Huh!
Next?
I'll go next.
Yawning prettily...
I wonder if there's a time to yawn.
Pretend you're a five-year-old.
It says "kindergarten student" on the front.
I'm going to put "kyan" on the garbage.
Who thinks of this?
Let's see how far we can go!
I'll do my best!
Momotaro grew up in no time
He grew up to be a fine
and became a gentle boy.
One day, Momotaro said to them
I heard that a wicked ogre lives on Onigashima Island.
I will go there and exterminate them.
Hearing that!
Granny made the most delicious yellow dumplings in Japan.
Momotaro put them in his waist pouch and set off for Onigashima!Momotaro put it in his waist pouch and immediately set off for Onigashima!
On the way, Momotaro entered the dog and asked
Momotaro-san, Momotaro-san, what's in the bag?
They are the best yellow dumplings in Japan!
Give me one and I'll eat it too!
It's a dog, it's a dog!
Momotaro...
Uh, what? Hmm? Meow!
Momotaro gave the dog a kibitango!
The dog became a keller!
And the same girl became a cackler.
The monkey and the pheasant also became keray!
Meow!
Please give me a break!
Really...
I hope you are fascinated with me?
If you are interested in the rest of the story, I hope we can do it again somewhere else. Thank you very much.
Meow!